gostats.com 2015-11-03

# GoStats | Privacy Statement

## GoStats Web Reporting Corp. Privacy Statement

Email Addresses
     Your email address will not be sold or used in ways to bother you with spam. GoStats requires a valid email address for your account in order to contact you regarding any changes with your GoStats account or to deliver your weekly stats email report. You can also learn more about [dealing with spam messages.](http://gostats.com/emailabuse.html)
Information Collection and Use
     GoStats is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. GoStats collects information from our users at several different points on our website. 
Registration
     In order to use this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest. It is optional for the user to provide demographic information (such as income level and gender), and other unique identifiers, but encouraged so we can provide a more personalized experience on our site. 
Order
     We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user may provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user. 
Cookies
     A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the cookie expires or is 'logged out', the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. For example, the user will not be able to view thier stats. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. 

Log Files
     We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 
Sharing
     We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. 
Links
     This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we Gostats are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 
Newsletter
     If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. 
Surveys & Contests
     From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. 
Tell-A-Friend
     If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend's name and email address. Gostats will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. Gostats stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email. The friend may contact Gostats at http://gostats.com to request the removal of this information from their database. 
Security
     This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line.

If our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just `surfing'.

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. 

If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can [contact gostats](http://gostats.com/contact.xml "Contact"). 

Special Offers
     We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members may occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please contact us for details. 
Site and Service Updates
     We also send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email. 
Correction/Updating Personal Information
     If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. This can usually be done at the member information page or by emailing our Customer Support. 
Notification of Changes
     If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 
Mailing Address
     North America: 428 Woolwich St. Waterloo, ON N2K 2L4 CA
